Guide to the Howard M. Spiro Papers
Medical Historical Library, Harvey Cushing / John Hay Whitney Medical Library
- Supplement: Publications by H. M. Spiro and Articles about H. M. Spiro
  - Editorials from G.I. Guide, edited by Howard Spiro, 1987-1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    File of editorials, similar in content to his columns is incomplete. Folder contains an entire issue for June 1987.